## Code Review

This is an excellent pull request that significantly improves the build quality and code robustness by enabling `-Werror` and fixing hundreds of existing warnings. The refactoring of the CMake build system to better manage compiler flags for core vs. driver code is a great step towards a more modular and maintainable project. The widespread use of `(void)` casts for unused parameters and `#if 0` for stubbed code is a clean way to handle the new strictness.

I've found two important issues that should be addressed: a critical use-after-free bug and an unsafe type cast that leads to modifying a `const` buffer. Please see the detailed comments below.
